Next, learn the core tool, sewing.
Open the library.
Then, in Connect the Cloud Training,
find the core tool, automatic sewing.
Double-click to open.
Then close the library.
This is a T-shirt that has been arranged.
Next, add a sewing line to the costume.
Select the automatic sewing tool.
You can automatically add a sewing line according to the type of costume.
Click on the small triangle next to the costume.
You can see that the type of costume can be divided into the top,
pants and skirt.
Here we choose the top.
And the front skirt type.
Select 5.
The front skirt line is selected on the left back side.
After selecting, click OK.
Now the costume has automatically added a sewing line.
We can also rotate the interface to check if the sewing line has been added correctly.
Finally, press the control grid on the keyboard to simulate.
The costume is ready to wear under the function of sewing line and gravity.
Press the control grid button again to close the simulation.
In addition to automatic sewing,
you can also use the sewing tool to increase the sewing line.
Complete the sewing box of various styles.
Open the library.
Then open the core tool, sewing.
Here you can choose whether.
Select confirm.
Close the library.
You can press the shortcut key on the keyboard.
You can see that there are sewing tools in the tools bar of 3D and 2D.
Therefore, you can sew in 3D or 2D windows.
Tools to add sewing lines.
There are sewing tools.
And there are two types of free sewing tools.
First of all, let's talk about sewing lines.
The sewing tool is the line and the line sewing.
Click to select the sewing tool.
You can see.
In windows 2D and 3D, you can add sewing lines.
Left mouse button.
Click one side of the line.
Add sewing line.
Then click another line.
Complete the sewing box of a sewing line.
When sewing.
You need to pay attention to the short mark on the sewing line.
It indicates the direction of the sewing.
We need to ensure that their directions are consistent.
Avoid an intersection.
When one line needs two.
Even when several lines are sewn together.
You can use a pair of more sewing.
First, you can click the left mouse button.
Select a long line.
Then press the Shift key on the keyboard.
Start to select more N lines.
The mouse is close to the other side.
You need to sew the line.
You can see.
At this time, the line has turned light green.
Click the mouse button to select one of the lines.
Be careful not to release Shift at this time.
Then select the second line.
In the process of sewing.
You need to pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
If there is an empty line of the sewing line at the moment.
There is an intersection.
And you can see in the 3D window.
The sewing line is screwed together.
It indicates that the sewing line direction at this time is opposite.
If you have finished sewing.
You can press Ctrl plus Z to withdraw the current operation.
If in the process of sewing.
A line is wrongly sewn.
You can delete it by pressing the Backspace key on the keyboard.
Be careful not to release Shift.
Continue to finish sewing.
Click the left mouse button.
After adding the sewing line.
You can release Shift to finish sewing.
When sewing multiple lines with multiple lines.
You can select the sewing line M to N.
Press the left mouse button.
Switch to sewing line M to N.
Then the left mouse button.
Click to select all M lines.
After completion, press back.
Complete the setting of M lines.
Then the left mouse button.
You can select all N lines.
In the process of choosing.
You also need to pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
After completion, press back.
Complete the setting of N lines.
At this time, the sewing line M to N is completed.
Then it is free sewing.
The free sewing tool is not controlled by the straight line point.
You can freely select the starting point and end point of the sewing line.
Press the switch tool to free sewing.
Then complete the sewing line addition here.
First come to the starting position.
Press start.
Then come to the other side.
Press the end.
Complete a sewing line.
The other side is also the left mouse button.
Press start.
Press the end.
So we have completed the addition of this sewing line.
Next, we will do one more free sewing.
We first press the start point on a long line.
At the end of the button.
It is necessary to pay attention.
When free sewing.
It is not necessary to add a sewing line according to the outline of the line.
You can directly click the start point and the end point.
Add the sewing line.
Then press the Shift key on the keyboard.
Start to select more N lines.
Be careful not to release Shift at this time.
In the process of sewing.
It is also necessary to pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
If there is a wrong sewing direction.
You can delete it by pressing the Backspace key on the keyboard.
Then add again.
Pay attention.
Do not release the Shift key throughout the process.
After the selection is complete.
Release the Shift key again to complete the sewing.
Next is M to N free sewing.
First, press the free sewing.
Switch tools to M to N free sewing.
Press the start point.
At the end of the button.
After the selection of all M lines is complete.
Press back.
Then.
Start to select all N lines.
After the selection of all N lines is complete.
Press back.
In the process of adding the sewing line.
It is also necessary to pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
Finally, the free sewing of M to N is completed.
If in the process of sewing.
There is a direction of the sewing line.
Add the wrong situation.
For example, here.
Let me show you.
We can use the edit sewing line tool.
Select the wrong sewing line.
Then press the delete key on the keyboard.
Delete the current sewing line.
If it is just the direction of the sewing line.
You can use the edit sewing line tool.
Select the sewing line.
Click the right key.
Choose to switch the sewing line.
You can see.
At this time, the direction of the sewing line.
It switched over.
Then.
Press the check the length of the sewing line tool.
There is a spring.
Here is divided into length difference and proportion difference.
We can check.
The length difference between the sewing lines.
To check whether the sewing line is correct.
This can prevent mistakes in the process of sewing clothing.
You can see.
The current length is 5 mm.
In other words, the length difference of the sewing line should be within 5 mm.
For example, adjust the sewing line.
The length difference is about 6 mm.
At this time.
The sewing line.
In the form of a red rough line.
With this hint.
The length of the sewing line is greater than 5 mm.
Cancel the selection length difference.
Only show the proportion difference.
The proportion difference is 10%.
The sewing line is no longer displayed as a red rough line.
Explain its length difference.
It is within the range of the proportion difference of the sewing line.
The number of length differences and proportion differences can be adjusted.
This is a tool for checking the length of the sewing line.
The above is the explanation of the sewing line tool.
Then explain the type of sewing line.
Press the Y on the keyboard to open the sketchbook.
Double-click to open the core tool.
The type of sewing line.
Close the sketchbook.
You can see.
The square panels that overlap together.
There is an obvious bulge at the seam of the panel.
Select the editing sewing line tool.
In the 2D window.
Select all sewing lines.
Then.
On the right side of the attribute editor.
You can see there is a seam.
Here.
Click on the seam.
And press the control key on the keyboard to open the simulation.
At this time.
The panel of the fold becomes flat.
Then.
When you make clothes.
Like the two-layer rawhide sleeve.
Or the style of making clothes.
You need to overlap the sewing line of the sewing part.
Open the fold.
Then.
You need to overlap the thing for the whole, except one.
You need to walk土.
I want.
You need to complete the whole.
OK.
Next.
Close a pouch.
You hide it.
You hide.
Cut it open.
Open too.
Close one more.
Open two more.
You hide it.
America is cried.